http://www.synova.ch/privacy-policy.html

Menu
Technology
Laser MicroJetTechnology BenefitsApplications
Main Application AreasEnergy & AviationTool ManufacturingDiamonds & JewelryWatchmakingMedicalSemiconductors & PhotovoltaicsMicro-MachiningProducts
All Synova SystemsMetal Cutting SystemsTool Cutting SystemsTurbine Drilling SystemsDiamond Cutting SystemsSemiconductor Dicing SystemsLMJ Integration PackageLMJ LicenseServices
Application DevelopmentJob ShopCustomer SupportCompany
About UsMicro-Machining Centers OEM PartnershipsR&D PartnershipsEventsNewsJobs & CareersContact
HeadquartersWorldwide
Search
Privacy Policy
Last updated: August 14, 2018
Welcome to Synova, and thanks for visiting our website!
We put together this privacy notice to let you know how we collect and process your personal data when you visit our company website and use third party services. By using www.synova.ch, you indicate your acceptance of this policy documented below. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our website. Your continued use of the website following the posting of changes to this policy will be considered as acceptance of those changes.
HOW AND WHY WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Synova may collect personal identification information from users in a variety of ways, including when you ask for information about our products or services, subscribe to our newsletter, download content, request marketing materials or provide us feedback.
Users may, however, visit the Synova website, LinkedIn, YouTube or other social media pages anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information.
HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Personal identification information is considered strictly confidential by Synova and will not be sold or passed on to third parties. Synova adopts appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on the website.
THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU
When accessing our web pages, the following data is stored in log files (on our web server managed by Cloudways, read their Privacy Policy (https://www.cloudways.com/en/terms.php#privacy): IP address, date, time, browser request and general transmitted information about the operating system resp. browser. These usage data form the basis for statistical, anonymous evaluations.
COOKIES
Synova uses cookies to track user's engagement with the website in order to continue to improve the website and provide better online experience.
THIRD PARTY SERVICES
We use Elastic Email to send emails from our website. For more information, read their Privacy Policy (https://elasticemail.com/resources/usage-policies/privacy-policy/).
We also use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc. (Google). Google Analytics uses cookies that allow an analysis of the use of the website. The information generated by the cookie about the page you have visited on this website is transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. Please note that on this website, Google Analytics code is supplemented by "anonymizeIp" to ensure an anonymized collection of IP addresses (so called IP-masking).
Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However, please note that if you do this, you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
You can prevent Google's collection and use of data by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB.
Further information concerning the Google Analytics terms and conditions of use and data privacy can be found at https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/gb.html or at https://policies.google.com/.
Please refer to this Privacy Policy regularly to keep up-to-date of any changes. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please email at: marketing@synova.ch
Synova is registered with the Registre du Commerce, Canton de Vaud, Switzerland. Our company identification number (IDE/UID) is: CHE-108.614.117
Registered Office:
Synova S.A.Route de Genolier 131266 Duillier, Switzerland
Contact Details:
Email: sales@synova.chPhone: +41 21 55 22 600
